



# Ashley Thompson



# CAREER OBJECTIVE

Having completed a Bachelor of Business (Information Systems) with highly developed customer service skills coupled with a passion for supporting people from all walks of life, I am actively pursuing a challenging full-time career opportunity as an Employment Consultant with Sarina Russo Group in a fast-paced, community-focused environment. I would greatly appreciate the opportunity to develop my skills whilst gaining recruitment skills and experience in a professional, customer-focused team environment. I am confident that you will find me to be a self-motivated, well presented individual with the capacity to conduct individual appointments with jobseekers face to face or using TEAMS or Zoom, achieve KPI's, organise appropriate interventions and strategies to help job seekers find and maintain employment, deliver high quality, timely, professional recruitment services to jobseekers.

# **KEY SKILLS & COMPETENCIES**

- Client Service: Provide quality client service and deliver tasks in order to meet best practice standards and client requirements.
- Communication: Excellent written and verbal communication skills, building relationships with internal and external personnel.
- Administration: Experienced in all aspects of administration management including record keeping scheduling and budgeting.
- Project Management: Plan and deliver projects to ensure time, cost, quality, safety expectations and requirements are met.
- Operations Management: Manage and optimise business operations across all areas, ensuring profitability objectives are met.

Stakeholder Management: Develop effective relationships and open communication to ensure stakeholders are well informed.

- Resource Management: Prepare accurate estimates of costs, human, physical and financial resources required for projects.
- Time Management: Well organised and highly efficient, with the ability to manage tasks, schedules and changing priorities.
- Process Development: Drives business innovation with a commitment to developing and improving processes and systems.
- Problem Solving: Undertake objective, critical analysis to draw accurate conclusions that recognise contextual issues.

# **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

#### Feb 2014 - Jun 2017

#### **BACHELOR OF BUSINESS (INFORMATION SYSTEMS)**

Full-time studies | Swinburne University, Hawthorn

#### 2017 Subjects:

- Social Entrepreneurship and Innovation
- Global Logistics & Supply Chain Management
- **Business Analytics**
- **Business Process Management**

#### 2016 Subjects:

- Management Decision Making
- Professional Issues in Information Technology
- Business Intelligence and Data Visualisation
- **Fundamentals of Marketing**
- **Database Systems**
- **Knowledge Management and Analytics**
- Information Systems Management
- **Business Information Systems Industry Project**

- Social Networking in Organisations
- Requirements Analysis & Modelling
- Information Systems Risk & Security
- Systems Acquisition & Implementation Management
- **Business Information Systems Analysis**
- Information Technology Project Management
- Careers in the Curriculum

#### 2014 Subjects:

- Mobile Business & Connectivity
- Financial Information for Decision Making
- Database, Analysis & Design
- Introduction to Programming IN .NET

Jan 2013 - Nov 2013

#### VICTORIAN CERTIFICATE OF EDUCATION

**Berwick Secondary College** 

**1** | Page Résumé of Ashley Thompson

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Dec 2015 - Current 1300 RESUME PTY LTD

Berwick, Victoria

**Customer Service Officer/Administration Officer (Part-time)** 

#### **Business Profile:**

1300 RESUME specialises in the provision of professional resumes, cover letters and selection criteria together with career and interview coaching for clients Australia wide from graduates to senior executives.

#### Responsibilities:

Over the past five years, I have dealt with jobseekers of all ages and from diverse cultural backgrounds across all industries via phone, email and skype to determine their needs, discuss their career goals and gather all required information for their résumé, cover letters and other associated documentation such as selection criteria. Furthermore, I utilise my high developed research and analytical skills to gather data and information from clients which assisted our Résumé Writers to write documents in an accurate manner.

Additionally, I perform general administration tasks such as filing, record keeping, formatting of documents, email management and social media management. In this role, I maintain and update computer databases on a regular basis using MS Access, designing Mail Chimp EDM campaigns using text, images and video on a monthly basis and assist with all social media marketing such as YouTube, Facebook and Linkedin as required.

Nov 2016 - Feb 2017 AUSTRALIAN AIR-CONDITIONING DISTRIBUTORS

Clayton, Victoria

Warehouse Assistant/Storeperson (Part-time/Casual)

#### **Business Profile:**

Australian Air-conditioning Distributors Pty Ltd (AAD) is a new generation of wholesaling that is completely focused on supporting the needs for trades people servicing the heating, ventilation and air-conditioning industry, covering commercial and residential sectors.

#### Responsibilities:

Whilst employed as a Warehouse Assistant/Storeperson, I performed a wide range of tasks which included unloading of goods and checking them against order forms, cataloguing or labelling items with storage details, place goods in bins and on racks or stack bulky items on floors in an organised manner.

Additionally, I completed orders by selecting goods from shelves and checking them off appropriate lists and entered details of received delivery slips, requisitions and invoices into computers. Using my organisation skills and attention to detail, I counted and recorded the number of items in store during stocktakes and advised the supervisor regarding any issues.

Feb 2008 - Dec 2010 ALL ABOUT IMAGE

Mornington Peninsula, Victoria

Administration & Marketing Assistant (Part-time)

## **Business Profile:**

All About Image was established in 1995, specialising in the provision of professional marketing, design and printing services to business clients including business cards, flyers and websites.

### Responsibilities:

In my employment as an Administration & Marketing Assistant, I managed front desk reception, providing friendly and courteous customer service via the telephone and face to face with clients as the first point of contact whilst providing information regarding services and packages. Drawing upon my communication and interpersonal skills, I consulted with small to medium business clients throughout the south-eastern suburbs of Victoria to gain a sound understanding of their visual communication requirements and develop design roughs and briefs which were provided to the Director for follow-up.

I prepared comprehensive layouts of business design using computer graphics programs such as Adobe Photoshop, searched and registered domain names for clients and provide quotations on website hosting. Furthermore, I was prepared designs for print then provided designs to clients via email in PDF format for approval and review whilst also coordinating all design production stages, ensuring artwork was prepared for the printer. Thriving in a deadline-driven environment, I managed multiple tasks and gained experience dealing with a broad range of people.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2012 CSIRO

Clayton, Victoria

#### Responsibilities:

I worked with a team of experienced IT professionals, involved in database management, provision of onsite support, deployment of computers, troubleshooting and liaise with internal staff to discuss their IT requirements.

2011 TROUT CREATIVE

Collingwood, Victoria

### Responsibilities:

I worked with a team of Graphic Designers, Web Designers and other creative personnel, involved in various tasks such as logo design and brand development, create advertisements, write reports, filing and general office duties. Drawing upon my communication and interpersonal skills, I liaise with business clients across various industries in conjunction with senior designers.

# PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

- Student Member of ISACA (Information Systems Audit and Control Association)
  - ISACA was incorporated in 1969 by a small group of individuals who recognized a need for a centralized source of information and guidance in the growing field of auditing controls for computer systems. Today, ISACA serves 140,000 professionals in 180 countries.

# **COMPUTER SKILLS**

- Mobile Technologies
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- Microsoft Access

- Microsoft Outlook
- Social Media Platforms
- Basic HTML & Coding
- Website Content Management
- Intermediate Networking
- Software & Hardware Installation
- Email & internet proficient
- Fast & accurate keyboard skills
- Proficient in various Windows OS
- Social Media Tools

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Nationality: Australian

**Date of Birth:** 5 November 1995

Licences Held: Current Victorian Driver's Licence and own reliable vehicle with an excellent driving record

Interests & Hobbies: Computers and technology, PC gaming, health, keeping fit, music, sports, spending

time with friends and family, movies, reading and meeting new people

# **PROFESSIONAL REFEREES**

**Monique Thompson** 

Director
1300 RESUME
Berwick, Victoria
90438 737 863

 Craig Vaughan

Warehouse Manager

Australian Air-conditioning Distributors

Clayton, Victoria

**2** 0429 992 903

**Kurt Thompson** 

Server Operations Engineer

**CSIRO** 

Clayton, Victoria

0438 881 592

4 | P a g e